RARES BUCUR

CONTACT

Address: Piata Victoriei nr. 4 (Relocation)

Phone: +40753307744

Email: rares.bucur99@yahoo.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/raresbucur

Website: https://raresbuc.github.io/RaresPortfolio/

SKILLS

- Experienced in multiple technologies and programming languages such as Autodesk Maya, Substance Painter, ZBrush, Blender, Unreal Engine, Photoshop, Python, JavaScript, C++, Git, Agile development
- I am always thinking about how I can digitally reproduce what I see in the physical world and I also spend a lot of my free time observing how others reproduce physical phenomena, especially within the video game industry and interactive media.
- The ability to adapt to every type of person in a professional manner through communication in order to get the task at hand done
- Being up to date to anything new in the industry by interacting in various communities and following a lot of video game and film related groups and channels
- I consider myself a perfectionist when it comes to work on a project I love
- Great attention to details
- Language skills: English (Professional Proficiency), Romanian (Native),
 French (Elementary Proficiency)

I have worked on multiple projects within and outside of my Computer Science degree programme, such as different CGI projects with a strong aim on prop and environment art development. I am able to create high poly hard-surface models with great attention to details and topology and a very good understanding of game art workflows including UV unwrapping, shading, texturing, lighting and rendering. I also have some experience with digital sculpting and organic modeling.

EDUCATION

University of Bristol

Bachelor's Degree - BSc, Computer Science (2019 - 2022)

Grade: Second Class with Honours (2:1)

"Unirea" National College

Romanian Baccalaureate Diploma: Maths - Computer Science (2015-2019)

Grade: 9.13 (Mathematics - 10, Physics - 9.6)

EXPERIENCE

University of Bristol

Teaching Assistant - Mathematics B (Jan 2021 - Jun 2021 & Jan 2022 - Jul 2022)

Helped a class of students getting through a series of lab sessions. Maintained weekly lab hours and problem-solving sessions.

Bristol Museum & Art Gallery

Frontend Developer (Nov 2020 - May 2021)

As a team of 4, I helped on creating a web application for the Bristol Museum & Art Gallery with the intention of showcasing what the museum has to offer and with the possibility of seeing the exhibits by searching through different art categories.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Jasmine Framework, AWS, Spring Boot

PORTFOLIO

Some projects from my portfolio (please see the full list by clicking on the portfolio)

Volkswagen Arteon R 2.0 TSI OPF 4Mot DSG (Link)

This is the premium model in the R-Line from Volkswagen. With elegant exterior styling that features an aerodynamic fastback design and a 320-hp turbocharged engine, you'll find the Arteon delivers a premium driving experience all its own. High-poly model with 4k textures made in Maya, textured in Substance, rendered in Vray.

Countryside by the river (Link)

I was inspired by a photo of a countryside I took a while ago. Sometimes all it takes is a small forest by the river to create a beautiful scenery. Composited and rendered in Unreal, with foliage from Quixel Megascans